<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<changelog>

    <release version="1.1.0" versioncode="11000">
        <change>NEW: Add "Close bubble" option to overflow menu.</change>
        <change>IMPROVEMENT: If the "Vibrate on touch" system setting is disabled, the app will not trigger any vibrations.</change>
        <change>BUG FIX: Many stability fixes.</change>
    </release>

    <release version="1.0.4" versioncode="10402">
        <change>BUG FIX: Many stability fixes.</change>
    </release>

    <release version="1.0.3" versioncode="10300">
        <change>NEW: Add option to set Link Bubble as the default system browser (assuming it is not already).</change>
        <change>IMPROVEMENT: Include the title of a webpage when sharing URLs.</change>
        <change>IMPROVEMENT: Increase time period required before "Close all" functionality kicks in when hovering over the Close bubble.
            Should address people unintentionally closing all their open tabs.</change>
        <change>IMPROVEMENT: "Close all" long press text uses Sans Serif font.</change>
        <change>IMPROVEMENT: Expand FAQ with entries about common questions such as how to close a tab quickly and why links may not be loading with Link Bubble.</change>
        <change>IMPROVEMENT: Add shortcut to Link Bubble Beta to the FAQ.</change>
        <change>CHANGE: Move FAQ to front page of the Settings to improve its visibility.</change>
        <change>CHANGE: Add shortcut to view my other apps to the Settings.</change>
        <change>BUG FIX: Fix case where YouTube embeds were sometimes not found on a page.</change>
        <change>BUG FIX: Many stability fixes.</change>
    </release>

    <release version="1.0.2" versioncode="10200">
        <change>NEW: Clicking the version number in the settings displays the full change log.</change>
        <change>CHANGE: Add a new 'Auto expand' checkbox to the settings. Replaces the previous (and confusing) 'Auto content display' setting.</change>
        <change>CHANGE: By default, links no longer automatically expand when they have finished loading.</change>
        <change>CHANGE: Free version no longer displays the notice about Link Bubble only handling links from a single app each time a link is
                loaded from the non-designated app. This prompt now only displays very rarely.</change>
        <change>BUG FIX: Many stability fixes.</change>
    </release>

    <release version="1.0.1" versioncode="10101">
        <change>Fix GPS usage for pages that request location (Note: Link Bubble itself never accesses your location).</change>
    </release>

    <release version="1.0.0" versioncode="10100">
        <change>Initial release.</change>
    </release>      
    
</changelog>
